A true story of faith, devotion and undying love.
Hachi: A Dog's Tale is a drama, family film directed by Lasse Hallström.
Professor Wilson discovers a lost Akita puppy on his way home.
Despite objections from his wife, Hachi endears himself to the
family and grows to be Parker's loyal companion.
As their bond grows deeper, a beautiful relationship unfolds.
Parker Wilson, played by Richard Gere.
Cate Wilson, played by Joan Allen.
Andy, played by Sarah Roemer.
Ken, played by Cary-Hiroyuki Tagawa.
Jasjeet, played by Erick Avari.
Michael, played by Robbie Sublett.
Hachi: A Dog's Tale is a 2009 American drama film and a remake of
Seijirō Kōyama's 1987 Japanese film Hachikō Monogatari.
The original film told the true story of the Akita dog
named Hachikō who lived in Japan 1923–1935.
Hachi: A Dog's Tale is an updated American
adaptation based on the Japanese film.
This version, which places it in a modern American context, was
directed by Lasse Hallström, written by Stephen P.
Lindsey and Kaneto Shindo, and produced by Richard Gere,
Bill Johnson and Vicki Shigekuni Wong.
The film stars Gere, Joan Allen, Sarah Roemer, Jason
Alexander, and Cary-Hiroyuki Tagawa.
Hachi: A Dog's Tale premiered at the Seattle International Film Festival on June 13,
2009, and its first theatrical release was in Japan on August 8, 2009.
The film was given a UK theatrical release on March 12, 2010, courtesy of Entertainment Film
Distributors, and opened in more than 60 countries throughout 2009 and 2010.
By the end of September 2010, the film's foreign box office
returns had totalled more than $45 million.
Sony Pictures Entertainment decided to forgo a U.S.
theatrical release, bringing the film out on DVD on March 9, 2010 and eventually
selling it to the Hallmark Channel, where it debuted on September 26, 2010.
The film explores themes of friendship, loyalty, pet, human
animal relationship, family relationships.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.